<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyCountryProfileDemo</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_button">Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="india_button">India</string>
    <string name="pakistan_button">Pakistan</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_text">
       Bangladesh is a country in South Asia. It shares land borders with India and Myanmar (Burma). \n
       Nepal, Bhutan and China are located near Bangladesh but do not share a border with it. \n
       The country\'s maritime territory in the Bay of Bengal is roughly equal to the size of its land area. \n
       Bangladesh is the world\'s eighth most populous country. \n
       Dhaka is its capital and largest city, followed by Chittagong, which has the country\'s largest port. \n
       Bangladesh forms the largest and easternmost part of the Bengal region.
   </string>
    <string name="india_text">
       India, officially the Republic of India is a country in South Asia. \n
       It is the seventh-largest country by area, the second-most populous country (with over 1.2 billion people), \n
       and the most populous democracy in the world. \n
       It is bounded by the Indian Ocean on the south, the Arabian Sea on the southwest,
       and the Bay of Bengal on the southeast. \n
       It shares land borders with Pakistan to the west; China, Nepal, and Bhutan to the northeast; \n
       and Myanmar (Burma) and Bangladesh to the east.
   </string>
    <string name="pakistan_text">
       Pakistan officially the Islamic Republic of Pakistan, is a country in South Asia. \n
       It is the fifth-most populous country with a population exceeding 209,970,000 people. \n
       In terms of area, it is the 33rd-largest country spanning 881,913 square kilometres (340,509 square miles). \n
       Pakistan has a 1,046-kilometre (650-mile) coastline along the Arabian Sea and Gulf of Oman in the south and is bordered by India to the east, \n
       Afghanistan to the west, Iran to the southwest, and China in the far northeast,
       respectively. \n
       It is separated narrowly from Tajikistan by Afghanistan\'s Wakhan Corridor in the north-west, \n
       and also shares a maritime border with Oman.
   </string>
</resources>
